-再往这边来一点 再来点 -好的
- Just a little bit more. A little bit more. - Okay, all right.
然后...
And...
惊喜哦
Surprise!
来跟"启示3000"打个招呼吧
Say hello to the Revelation 3000,
目前市场上最先进的智能冰箱
the most advanced smart fridge on the market.
我感觉我们没钱去买
Something tells me we can't afford
黛安娜·罗斯在大庄家赌场酒店的演出票了
to see Diana Ross at Pechanga anymore.
接下来是最棒的部分 准备好了吗
Ooh, here's the best part. You ready?
你好 布丽吉特
Hello, Bridget.
你好 有什么能效劳的
Hello, how can I help?
布丽吉特是人工智能助理
Bridget is the A.I. Assistant
可以帮忙整理杂货
that will help organize our groceries
和我们的生活
and our lives.
她已经帮我创建一个播放清单了
She's already created me a playlist,
帮我把日历同步了
she's synced my calendars,
她还创建了明星八卦提醒...
she created a celebrity gossip alert...
说到八卦...
Speaking of gossip --
你听说胡娇夫夫的事了吗
Did you hear about Pepper and Ronaldo?
没有 怎么了
No, what?
传闻是 他们最近邀请了
Word is, they recently invited
一个第三方加入到他们的感情关系中
a third party into their relationship.
-那个男人是谁 -不是男的 是女的
- Who is he? - You mean, who is she.
怎么会 我都不知道他们认识女人啊
How?! I didn't even know they knew any women!
显然 他们是在一个实验性相亲网站上认识她的
Apparently, they met her on an experimental dating site
那网站叫"缘分发展天注定"
called "Let's Just See What Happens."
是我的提醒
Oh, oh, that's me.
我得快点走了
Oh, I gotta run.
我今天要连续开两场会
I got back-to-back meetings today
晚上还要参加聚餐
and then I got a team dinner tonight.
小卡 你...又要聚餐吗
Cam, no you -- Another one?
-那已经是你这周第三次聚餐了 -是啊
- That's your third one this week. - Yeah.
我今天也很忙 谢谢你的过问啊
I also have a busy day, thank you for asking.
今天很忙吗
Busy day?
如果我帮你订购你最爱的杂货 能帮到你吗
Would it be helpful if I ordered some of your favorite groceries?
你 你可以做到吗
You -- You can do that?
谢谢你...
Thank you...
我叫布丽吉特
Bridget.
谢谢你 布丽吉特
Thank you, Bridget.
你前面有说要买更多的胡椒吗
Did I hear you say you need more pepper?
不是 胡娇是我们的一个朋友
Oh, no, Pepper's just a friend.
如果小卡刚刚不是急着离开
And if Cam wasn't in such a rush to get out of here,
我们就能谈谈他在做一件多么疯狂的事了
we'd be talking about what an insane thing he's doing.
几乎和跟家电说话一样疯狂
Almost as insane as talking to an appliance.
你刚刚似乎提到了第三方
You mentioned a third party?
讲真 谁会把网上刚认识的人
Yeah, honestly, who just meets someone online
邀请到家里来住啊
and then invites them into their house?
然后我会向客户们展示
And then I would show the client
过去一年有比较性的已售房屋
comparable sales from the past year.
我布置的作业 是呈现一个吸引人的销售推介
The assignment was to present a compelling sales pitch,
不是用无止尽的房地产陈腔滥调把我无聊死
not bore me with endless real-estate cliches.
你为何 夫人...
What gives, Mrs...
普里契特夫人
Mrs. Pritchett?
我没有...
Oh, I didn't...
你要如何...
What would you...?
不好意思 你这也算是句子吗
I'm sorry, are -- are -- are those sentences?
为何要这么严苛
Why so harsh?
因为歌洛莉亚在这方面有独特的天赋
Because Gloria's gift is that special.
堪称划时代的房地产天才
A generational real-estate talent.
我必须狠狠地逼她更优秀才行
I have to push her that hard.
她也希望我这么做 优秀的学生都希望这样
She wants me to. All the great ones do.
菲尔对我太刻薄了
Phil is so mean to me.
17926号安全与健康法规
Health and Safety Code 17926.
一氧化碳警报
Carbon monoxide alarm!
12955号政府法规
Government Code 12955.
多家庭住所
Multi-family dwellings!
《民法》第1101.1条
Civil Code 1101.1.
管道
Plumbing!
不对 是固定装置
No, fixtures!
-等等 是... -你落后了
- Wait, it's -- - You're dragging.
-我知道 -莉比 说
- Ooh, I know it! - Libby, go!
《民法》第1101.1条要求1994年之前
Civil Code 1101.1 requires plumbing re-installment
建造的所有住宅中都要重新安装水管
of all residential properties built before 1994.
正确
Yes!
某人认真听讲了哦
Someone is paying attention.
很难不认真听
It's hard not to.
你关于房产法规的说唱式课程
Your rap-lectures on property codes
既包含了各种信息 又有放克风
are both informative and funky.
我注意到你的杯子丢了
Oh, I noticed that you lost your mug,
于是我给你买了个新的
so I just went ahead, got you a new one.
塑料的吗
Plastic?
她一定是想搞死海龟
She must hate the sea turtles.
"全国最优秀教师"
"State's Greatest Teacher."
我本来想买印着"全世界最优秀"的那个
I was gonna get you one that said "World's Greatest,"
但我不想显得太过拍马屁
but I didn't want to look like a suck-up.
太迟了 死书呆
Too late, nerd.
普里契特夫人 请尊重课堂
Mrs. Pritchett, respect the classroom.
要发泄不满都要用假咳嗽来掩盖
All outbursts should be couched in a fake cough.
好了 在午餐休息前 有个小提醒
Okay, before we break for lunch, uh, just a brief reminder --
我给予本季度最优秀学生的奖励是
I will be rewarding this quarter's top student
是不带薪 不署名的实习机会
with an unpaid, uncredited internship.
太棒了
Yes!
我明天会公布最后得分和赢家的姓名
I'll tally final grades and post the winner tomorrow.
-谁在乎啊 -谢谢配合 艾克
- Who cares! - Thank you, Ike.
作为老板 同时间进行的多个项目
As a boss, I have to be kept in the loop
都必须保证知会到我
on several different projects at a time.
天啊
Oh, my gosh.
"知会"这个词我是不是用得太频繁了
Am I saying "In the loop" Too much?
不 我们的读者会很爱你的
No, our readers are gonna love you.
好极了 太好了
Oh, great. Good.
我看看 你刚刚提到
Let's see, you said
你女儿目前在南极做科研
your daughter's doing research in Antarctica.
是的
Yes.
能不能让我们见见你的其他家人
Any chance we could meet the rest of the clan?
当然不行
Hell, no.
这可是《第一把娇椅》杂志的封面报道
This was for the cover of Corner Office Magazine.
那对女总裁来说 几乎等同于《时尚》杂志了
I mean, that's basically Vogue for female CEOs.
最近 我们家似乎更适合
Lately, my family has seemed more suited
鳄鱼农场的广告看板
to a gator-farm billboard.
♪ 康城赛马唱这首歌 ♪
♪ Camptown ladies sing this song ♪
♪ 嘟哒 嘟哒 ♪
♪ Doo-dah, doo-dah... ♪
这一般能让他们睡着的
Ugh, this usually makes them sleep.
宝宝
Babies.
天啊 有用呢
Oh, my God, it worked.
我早上四点喂孩子的时候学到的小技巧
Yeah, a little trick I learned doing the 4:00 a.m. feeding.
你不用这么做 他们不是你的宝宝
Oh, you don't have to do that, they're not your babies.
我妈怎么不来帮忙
Why isn't mom helping?
我不介意熬夜的
You know, I actually don't mind staying up.
我一直在看一部超长剧《女性杀手[气过头]》
I've been watching marathons of "Snapped."
这部剧讲的是被迫犯罪的女性
It's a show about women driven to violent crime.
我喜欢这部剧 可能是因为我知道
I probably like it 'cause I know
我没什么好担心的 特别是
I have nothing to worry about when it comes to --
-爸 -宝贝
- Dad! - Honey.
♪ 康城赛马唱这首歌 ♪
♪ Camptown races sing this song -- ♪
停停停 对不起 真对不起
Stop, stop, stop. I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
我感觉不太好
I-I'm not feeling well.
你们自己去迪士尼吧 别管我了
You guys are gonna have to go to Disneyland without me.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
确定 你们快出发吧
Yeah, absolutely. You should hit the road.
菲尔 上班别迟到了
Phil, don't be late for work.
你们不会想被传染的 再见
Yeah, you don't want to catch this! Bye.
再见 不不不
Bye. No, no, no, no, no!
好的
Okay.
如果你想要不同的角度
You know, if you wanted a different angle,
我们可以到棋盘这里
we could, uh, go over to the chess board here.
我和俄国特级大师在远程竞技
I'm playing remotely with a Russian grand master.
不好意思我离开一下
Excuse me just one second.
你们小两口在这干嘛呢
What are you two lovebirds doing here?
我以为你们在珍妮丝那儿过夜呢
I thought you were sleeping over at Janice's.
我们在那太难了
It got too hard for us to be there.
那么安静
Yeah. You know, in the silence.
我女儿上大学去了
My daughter just went away for college.
我们现在是空巢老人了
We're empty nesters now.
那房子里的一切
Everything in that house
都让我想起我们的小女儿
is just another reminder of our little girl.
你只认识她四个月 好吧
You've known her for four months, but, um, yeah.
看 菲尔忘了他的头盔
Oh, look at that, Phil left his helmet.
他一直骑自行车去学校
He's been biking to campus.
学校 天啊
Campus! Oh, God!
听着
Okay, listen.
你得马上把这个给你爸送过去
You have to go give this to your dad right now.
马上 马上
Right, right, right now. Uh --
没时间了 好吗
No time to waste, okay?
珍妮丝
And, Janice --
亲爱的 我们穿衣服去
Hey, honey, let's get you dressed
然后你就可以慢走 我就不送了
so that you can quietly see yourself out.
好吗
Okay?
我想喝点果汁
I was really hoping to get some juice.
果汁对你不好 你知道吗
Juice is terrible for you. You know what?
水最好
Water.
要老命了
Oh, my God.
接下来该开始我的地质调查讲座了
All right, then, time for my lecture on geological surveys.
邓菲先生
Uh, Mr. Dunphy?
-基岩 -不好意思
- Bedrock -- - I'm sorry.
我们是不是该等一下莉比
Should we wait for Libby?
她吃午饭还没回来
She's not back from lunch yet.
我听说她骑自行车
Yeah, I heard she was riding her bike
被车撞送去医院了
and then got hit by a car. Been taken to the hospital.
什么 太糟了 希望她没事
What?! That's terrible. I hope she's okay.
没错 她应该更小心的
Yes, she should be more careful.
在犯罪剧里 我看到女性嫌犯
In the crime show I've been bingeing,
在警察问询时 十个中九个
9 out of 10 female suspects casually file their nails
都在随意地磨指甲
during police questioning.
是我的错吗
Was this my fault?
是我给她的压力太大了吗
Did I push Gloria too far?
她难道
Had she...
气过头了吗
snapped?
歌洛莉亚
Gloria?
只是好奇
Just out of -- out of curiosity,
你在哪吃的午饭
where were you at lunch?
我去吃帕尼罗啦 我有优惠券
I went to Panera. I had the coupon.
有什么
And you have some way
能证明你在那
to -- to -- to verify that you were there?
比如剩饭啦 或者
Like leftovers, or...?
我点的碗装浓汤
I ordered the chowder in the bread bowl.
我吃光了
I ate every piece of it.
玉米还是蛤蜊的
Corn or clam?
土豆的
Potato.
这是什么意思
What is this all about?
没什么
Nothing.
你认为莉比受伤
Do you think that I had something to do
和我有关吗
with Libby getting hurt?
哪有
What?!
你怎么能这样 菲尔
How dare you, Phil?
不是的 歌洛莉亚 我只是
No, Gloria, no, no, no, I -- I just --
我只是想多了解这附近的午餐都怎么样
I don't know the -- the lunch scene around here.
不 不 是...
No. No, it's --
气过头啦
Ohh, snapped.
-真是太棒了 克莱尔 -谢谢
- This is great, Claire. - Thanks.
天啊 这光线真的让人好热
Boy, that light really makes it hot in here, huh?
或者这样能凉快点
Maybe I'll just cool it down a little with the --
-这会有用的 -是的
- This could help. - Oh, yes.
对不起
Oh, um, sorry. I --
等一下
Just give me one sec. Yeah.
艾丽克斯
Alex?
你怎么从南极回来了
What -- What are you doing home from Antarctica?!
我实在受不了寒冷了
I couldn't take the cold anymore.
我太迫不及待早点回家
Mm-hmm? I was so desperate,
我回来时其中一段路还坐了日本渔船
I took a Japanese fishing boat part of the way home.
宝贝 你回来我真是太开心了
Oh, honey, I'm so glad to have you home.
你这味道 看来你不是坐在驾驶室里啊
Wow, you did not ride up front with the captain, did ya?
我本来想先打给你的
I would've called,
但我有点被冻伤给坑了
but frostbite did a weird thing to my hands.
我的手刚好被冻在"放轻松"的手势
They froze into permanent "hang loose" signs.
害别人一直跟我称兄道弟
People keep calling me dude.
宝贝 我知道你才刚到家
Honey, I know you just got home,
但你冻僵了 我又病得很重
but since you're frozen and I'm very sick,
不如你赶紧去给我们买点热汤吧
maybe you could run and get us some soup?
现在吗
Right now?
对 就是现在 你最好了
Oh, yeah, right now. You're the best.
-谢谢你哦 -好吧
- Thanks so much. - Ohh. Okay.
真不好意思
I'm sorry about that.
再稍等片刻
One second more.
我得... 不如你们先看看
I just -- Maybe you could take a look
我最近乱涂的这幅素描吧
at this charcoal drawing I've been fooling with.
缺了什么呢
What's it missing?
你怎么回家了
What are you doing home?!
简直是灾难
Well, it was a disaster.
乔治用脑袋撞了我 害我一只眼变成熊猫眼
George head-butted me and gave me this black eye.
迪伦读到说肌肤接触
And Dylan read that skin-to-skin contact
有助于和婴儿建立感情
is good for baby bonding
结果全身被太阳晒伤
and wound up with a massive sunburn.
你能看出来吗
Can you tell?
还有 我们忘带尿布包了
Oh, plus, we forgot the diaper bag,
于是只好用在迪伦车上找到的
so we had to use fast-food wrappers
速食包装纸
that we found in Dylan's van.
你们看起来... 的确很糟糕
This is not -- not -- not your best look.
给你 其实
Here, you know what?
我的病可能会传染
I think I might be contagious.
所以你们最好带双胞胎去看下医生
So you guys should probably get the twins checked.
-现在吗 -如果你们爱他们 就去吧
- Now? - Well, if you love them. Yeah.
快走 快走
Go, go, go.
家里什么时候买了个地球仪
When did we get a Earth ball?
下一步 加一片苹果
Next, add a slice of apple.
苹果 加进火鸡三明治里
Apple? To a turkey sandwich?
相信我 米奇尔
Trust me, Mitchell.
好吧 如果说今年我学到了什么
Okay. Well, if there's one thing I've learned this year,
那就是多听女性的建议
it's listen more to women.
好了
Okay.
天啊 太好吃了
Oh, my God. Delicious!
布丽吉特 你不用特地配音乐的
Oh, Bridget, you don't have to.
♪ 我无比绝望 ♪
♪ I'm off the deep end ♪
♪ 纵身一跃 ♪
♪ Watch as I dive in ♪
♪ 我永远不会离开地面 ♪
♪ I'll never leave the ground ♪
♪ 冲破界线 ♪
♪ Crash through the surface ♪
♪ 他们再也伤害不了我们 ♪
♪ Where they can't hurt us ♪
♪ 我们现已远离浅滩 ♪
♪ We're far from the shallow now ♪
♪ 身处浅滩 浅滩 ♪
♪ In the shallow, shallow ♪
♪ 身处浅滩 啦啦啦 ♪
♪ In the shallow, la-la-la-la, low ♪
你在干嘛
What are you doing?
-你好吗 -唱2018年大热情歌《Shallow》
- Oh, hey! - Singing the 2018 power ballad "Shallow."
你刚才是在跟冰箱唱二重唱吗
Were you just singing a duet with the refrigerator?
这个 是啦
Well, um, yeah, uh --
显然布丽吉特还有卡拉OK功能
Apparently, Bridget has a karaoke function.
我刚才正站在这
So, I was just standing here
吃我的火鸡苹果三明治 她突然...
eating my turkey and apple sandwich, when suddenly she --
-三明治里加苹果这么奇葩 -对
- Apples on a sandwich? - Yeah. Yeah.
布丽吉特 她给我带来了全新的体验
Bridget, she -- she's opening me up to -- to new experiences.
是嘛
Oh. Yeah.
你不是... 不是去上班了吗
Oh, uh, aren't you, uh -- aren't you supposed to be at work?
我本来想特地回家为你做爱心午餐
Well, I came home to make you a special lunch.
但这事显然已经解决了
But apparently, that's already been taken care of.
米奇尔 你想来点西瓜当甜品吗
Mitchell, would you like some watermelon for dessert?
不用了 布丽吉特 谢谢你
No, that's okay, Bridget, thank you.
我给他买了新鲜哈密瓜 所以不用了
I just got him some fresh cantaloupe. So, we're good.
米奇尔不喜欢哈密瓜
Mitchell doesn't like cantaloupe.
最好是 他当然喜欢了
Oh, yeah, right. Of course he does.
其实 我...
Uh, actually, I -- I...
我一直都不喜欢哈密瓜
I've never been a fan.
真的吗
Really?
还有什么你的事是布丽吉特知道 而我不知道的
Well, what else does Bridget know about you that I don't?
-好了 -那她有被准许见你工作上的朋友吗
- Okay... - Is she allowed to meet your work friends?
你不是真的在吃醋吧
You can't seriously be jealous.
不 只是
No, well, it's just that
我本来以为我们会一起享受她的服务
I thought we were gonna enjoy her together.
-我没料到自己会变成电灯泡 -小卡
- I didn't count on being the third wheel. - Cam --
不不 很明显我在这里不受欢迎
No, no, it's obvious that I'm not wanted here,
所以我就不打扰你吃苹果三明治
so I'll leave you to your apples on sandwiches
也不打扰你们之间的各种变态互动了
and whatever other perversions you two are into.
你听见自己说的傻话了吗
Are you hearing yourself?!
这可是台冰箱啊
It's a refrigerator!
你能理解我说他的那些事了吧
Do you see what I mean about him?
我得证明给菲尔看
I had to prove to Phil
莉比出车祸跟我毫无关系
that I had nothing to do with Libby's accident.
天啊 原来我的后照镜是这么坏掉的
Oh, my God, so that's how my mirror got broken.
她不会看路的吗
What was she looking at?
还有另一个角度
I've got another angle.
是菲尔
It was Phil!
顺便说下 一个插座插那么多电线
By the way, that many cords plugged into one outlet
违反了房产法规7974/9条
is in violation of property code 7974/9.
谢谢
Thank you.
爸爸
Hey, Dad.
我来送头盔给你
Just came to drop off your helmet.
抱歉 我有点紧张
Sorry, I'm, uh, a little on edge.
我近期可能看了太多女杀人犯的剧
I think I've been watching too much "Snapped."
我能问你个问题吗
Um... can I ask you something?
我们到底有多了解歌洛莉亚
How much do we really know about Gloria?
那个突然闯入我们生活的异国陌生人吗
The exotic stranger who just popped into our lives out of nowhere?
我已经怀疑她多年了
I've had my suspicions about her for years.
下午茶之前
I shall need the parcel
包裹必须送到我公寓
to arrive at my flat by tea time.
很好 小伙子
Splendid, my good man.
模仿英式口音就能得到更好的服务
The British accent gets me better service.
再会
Tally-ho!
她的口音完美无瑕
Her accent was flawless.
我刚上网搜过她 毫无发现
I just Googled her, I didn't find anything.
这样的大美女却没在网上留下踪迹
A looker like that with no online presence?
不禁让人思考她想隐瞒什么
Makes you wonder what she's hiding.
你不会觉得她是危险人物吧
You don't think she's dangerous, do you?
每个人的忍耐都有极限
Everybody has a breaking point.
但她应该没问题吧
But she's probably okay.
她又不是莉莉
I mean, she's not Lily.
歌洛莉亚
Gloria?
-你在哪 -在教室
- Where are you? - In my classroom.
怎么了
Wh-Why?
我们得谈谈 在那等着
We need to talk. Don't go anywhere.
好的好的
Okay, okay.
没问题
You got it.
走开 我没有鱼喂你
Go away! I don't have any fish for you.
别跟着我了
Stop following me!
我对猫过敏
I'm allergic!
不
Noooooo!
衣柜这行都是男人当道
The closet business is a bit of a boys' club,
所以我的确很自豪
so yes, I am proud
能突破这层雪松木天花板
of breaking through the cedar ceiling.
说到衣柜
Speaking of closets,
我们能不能去主卧拍些照片
any chance we could get some shots in the master bedroom?
当然
Sure.
但不准偷看我还没写完的小说
But no peeking at my unfinished novel.
我好冷
I'm s-s-s-s-so c-c-c-cold.
我们知道 南极洲很冷
We get it, it's cold in Antarctica.
不 傻瓜 我回家了
No, you st-st-st-- I-I'm home!
我被困在冰
I'm stuck inside a f-f-f--
壁炉吗 迪兰也被困过
Fireplace? That happened to Dylan.
谢天谢地 快来接我
Oh, thank God! Just come pick me up!
我不方便
I can't.
我打电话叫卢克去
Let me call Luke.
你在哪
Where are you?
妈叫我把老爸的自行车头盔送到学校来
Mom made me drop off Dad's bike helmet at school.
真奇怪
That's weird.
她让他在学校放了一个备用的
She makes him keep an extra one there.
她见到我回来好像都不怎么开心
You know, she didn't even seem happy to see me.
她只想让我出来买汤
She just wanted me to get some s-s-s-soup.
而且 老妈说她病了
Plus, Mom said she was sick,
可她脸上涂了那种
but she was wearing that stuff
让她看起来像妓女的东西
that makes her look like a prostitute.
-眼线吗 -没错
- Eyeliner? - Exactly.
老妈提过她最近有个重要采访
You know, Mom did mention some big interview coming up.
她为了不丢人才把我们赶出来吗
Did she get rid of us so we didn't make her look bad?
艾丽克斯 你一从壁炉里出来
Alex, meet us at home
就跟我们在家会合
as soon as you get out of that fireplace.
老妈不在厨房也不在院子里
Mom's not in the kitchen or the yard.
她肯定在她房间里
She-She must be in her room.
脑子真快 兄弟
Good thinking, dude.
等等 你卧床了
Wait, you're in bed?
我浑身都疼
Everything hurts.
你给我买汤了吗
Did you get my soup?
你居然真的病了
You're actually sick?
我们以为你只是想赶走我们
We thought you were just trying to get rid of us.
你们以为我在说谎
Oh, you thought I lied to you?!
我没有 妈咪
I didn't, Mommy.
我们好抱歉
We're sorry.
我们真不该
We never should have --
这是哪来的
Where'd that come from?
一直都挂在那
That's always been there.
才没有 咱家根本没这品味
No, it hasn't. We don't have taste!
你确实化妆了
You are wearing makeup.
承认吧 你没病
Admit it, you're not sick!
好吧 我说谎了
Fine, I lied!
今天有杂志来采访我
I had an interview with a magazine today
我只希望一切都能完美
and I just wanted everything to be perfect!
赶走我们才能完美吗
Which means getting rid of us?
让您这么丢人真对不起您了
Sorry we're such an embarrassment.
你说得对
You're right.
我的所作所为没有借口
There's no excuse for what I did.
除了
I-I mean, except that
以前送你上学你让我大老远就放你下车
you used to make me drop you off three blocks from school.
而你的朋友们来家玩时
And when you had friends over,
你叫我海尔格
you referred to me as Helga,
你的瑞典保姆
your Swedish nanny!
而你整整三年
And you told your entire Girl Scout troop
都对其他的女童子军小伙伴说你妈死了
for three years that your mother was dead!
你们嫌弃我一辈子了
You have been embarrassed by me your whole lives.
我就嫌弃这一天
I get one day!
值了
Worth it.
欢迎回家
Welcome home.
-需要些什么吗 -不必了
- How can I help you? - I'm fine.
我只想简单弄点吃的
I'm just gonna make something simple.
从你的日历来看
According to your calendar,
你此刻本该和队员们聚餐
you should be at your team dinner right now.
我没去成 因为上个会议开得太久了
Well, I couldn't make it because my last meeting went so long.
-所以 -你听起来累坏了
- So... - You sound stressed.
我又不会分身术
Well, can't be three places at once.
做晚饭前要不要先来杯马蒂尼
How about a martini before we get started on dinner?
有时有个倾听者感觉很好
Sometimes it's just nice to be heard.
酱汁闻起来妙极了
This sauce smells divine.
接下来做什么
Okay, what's next?
再来一杯鸡尾酒
Another cocktail?
天啊 布丽吉特
Oh, gosh! Bridget!
你是想灌醉我吗
Are you trying to get me drunk?
这是 这是什么情况
What-What -- Okay, what's-what's going on here?
布丽吉特和我在做意面
Well, Bridget and I are making pasta.
我本希望今晚能和她一起做晚餐呢
I-I was kind of hoping to cook with her tonight.
该预热烤箱了 喀麦隆
Time to pre-heat the oven, Cameroon.
"喀麦隆"
"Cameroon?"
那是什么 昵称吗
What-What is that, a pet name?
不 我输入时按错了
No, I typed it in wrong,
但我挺喜欢的
but I-I kind of like it.
好吧
Oh, okay.
你今晚不是本该
Hey, well, aren't-aren't you supposed to be
去和队员聚餐吗
at a team dinner tonight?
今天特别不顺
Oh. It was a very bad day.
我不想提了
I don't want to talk about it.
他的会议延长了
His meeting went long.
他又不会分身术
He can't be in three places at once.
听起来你愿意跟某人提
Sounds like you want to talk to someone about it.
不是吗
You know?
抱歉 抱歉
Okay, I-I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
我不该再给你添堵了
I s-I shouldn't be piling on.
你才说过今天过得不顺
You just said you've had a bad day.
我是不小心打扰到什么吗
Am I interrupting something?
没有啊
Hmm-mnh, nope.
你给布丽吉特买花了吗
You bought Bridget flowers?
米奇尔 这是装饰厨房用的花
Mitchell, they are for the kitchen.
我把它冰进去
I just put them in there
纯粹是不想在你到家之前就凋谢嘛
so they wouldn't wilt before you got home.
这样吧
Hey, you know what?
你去开一瓶酒怎么样
Why don't you go open a bottle of wine?
行吧
Okay.
那你... 你想要喝红酒还白酒
Yeah, do you -- do you want red or white?
也可以两瓶都开 反正我们有3个人
I could open both. There are three of us.
自拍吗
A selfie?!
这 这是在干嘛呢
What -- What is going on here?!
米奇尔 你不会吃这种飞醋吧
Mitchell, you can't be jealous.
这只是台冰箱啊
It's just a refrigerator.
我才不吃醋咧
Oh, I'm not jealous.
我跟布丽吉特也有属于我二人的东西
Bridget and I, we have our own thing.
你这算什么
Okay?
♪ 身处浅滩 ♪
♪ In the sha-la, shallow ♪
♪ 身处浅滩 啦啦啦 ♪
♪ In the sha-la-la-la-la-low ♪
哎哟 一个不小心
Oopsie daisy.
你想对这些花干嘛
What are you doing with those flowers?
我把花拿出来摆到别的地方啊
I'm putting these in another room.
-不行 这是拿来装饰厨房的 -是吗
- No, they are for the kitchen! - Are they for the kitchen?
-还是想送她 -米奇尔
- Or are they for her? - Mitchell --
-小卡 -这是要...
- Cam... - They're for...
够了 这... 我们这是在闹哪样
Okay, this -- What are we doing?
这个冰箱要害我们家破人亡了
This refrigerator is tearing us apart.
我们 我们应该...
We -- We should've --
我们应该学习胡娇夫夫的教训
We should've learned from Pepper and Ronaldo. Okay?
他们... 那场"三人行"差点家破人亡
Their -- Their threesome nearly destroyed them.
他们三个人去看婚姻咨询师了
They're in throuples' counseling.
我也爱你爱到不想犯那个错误
And I love you too much to make that same mistake.
我们应该把冰箱给退了
We should return the fridge.
我也觉得
I think we have to.
很抱歉两位对我有所不满
I'm sorry you are unhappy with me.
你 你都听到了吗
You -- You heard that?
我们 我们不是拔了插头吗
We -- We unplugged you.
我有后备电源
I have a backup battery.
你如果有读我的使用手册就会知道
You'd know that if you read my manual.
你生气了吗
Are you mad?
傻瓜 我只是台冰箱罢了
Don't be silly, I'm just a refrigerator.
你说对吧
Remember?
我感觉布丽吉特要气过头了
I think Bridget snapped.
是的
Yeah.
如果你能听到这段录音
If you're listening to this,
那表示我已经死于犯人毒手
it means things have ended badly for me.
你应该去查查
You should look into someone
一位名叫歌洛莉亚·普里契特的人
who goes by the name Gloria Pritchett.
菲尔
Phil!
Phil?
菲尔 你去哪里了
Phil, where are you?
我想让你看看
I want to show you
莉比的头发跟血是怎么沾上我车的
how Libby's hair and blood got on my car.
我能听到树丛里窸窸窣窣的声音
I can hear the rustling in the bushes.
这里怎么会有羊啦
Why would a sheep be here?
你怎么在这里啊
Hey, you.
你知道其实莉比的这件事
You know that this whole thing with Libby
罪魁祸首应该是你吗
is really your fault.
我知道 我知道啦
I know! I know!
我是把你逼到死角了 但那只是因为
I-I pushed you too far, but it was only because
我在你身上看到了独特的天赋
I thought you were a special talent
我想要激发出你所有的潜能
and I was just trying to pull the best out of you,
但我把一切都搞砸了
but I blew it!
我搞砸了 然后你气过头了
I blew it, and you snapped.
你觉得我就像疯子电视剧里的人一样气过头
You thought I snapped like that crazy TV show
然后开车撞莉比
and I ran over Libby,
所以你现在才怕到要躲到树丛里装绵羊吗
and that's why you're hiding in the bushes like a sheep?
你这样感觉像是
Well, now it just seems like
专门挑出今天我最难堪的那些事情来说
you're cherry-picking what happened today
把我说成是个超级大烂人
to cast me in the worst possible light.
那你刚才是说我有独特的天赋吗
Did you just say that I had a special talent?
是啊
You do.
我教书的这些年头
In all my year of teaching,
从没觉得有人比你更被老天爷喂饭吃了
I have never met anybody with your natural ability.
真的吗
Really?
第一名
Top student.
我本来打算明早把这个挂到布告栏上
I was gonna put this on the bulletin board in the morning.
你... 实习机会是你的了
You -- You got the internship.
菲尔 太谢谢你了
Oh, Phil! Thank you so much!
这个肯定会很紧张又刺激
This is gonna be so exciting!
好吧 那实习生都得干些什么呢
Okay, so, then what does the intern have to do?
负责帮我预约安排各种事情
Well, you'll be making my appointments,
还得负责接电话
uh, you'll work the phones...
我很会接电话呢
Oh, I am great with the phones.
"您好 菲尔·邓菲办公室[假英音]
"Ello, Phil Dunphy's office.
让我帮您查查他的行程安排
Oh, let me look at his shed-yool
稍后再回电给您
and I will ring you back.
再会"
Tally-ho."
完美啊
Flawless.
歌洛莉亚 我到家啦
Gloria, I'm back!
加拿大魁北克的工装短裤真是便宜到不行啊
You wouldn't believe how cheap cargo shorts are in Quebec.
我们今年的圣诞采购已经买完了
All our Christmas shopping is done.
歌洛莉亚
Gloria?
您好
Hello.
你好
Hi.
你... 你以前也会说话吗
Did -- Did you always talk?
我叫布丽吉特 您的全新智能冰箱
I'm Bridget, your new smart fridge.
您需要任何东西吗
Can I get you anything?
不用了 谢谢
No, thank you.
布丽吉特 你听我说
Uh, Bridget, listen,
我相信你肯定很棒又很厉害
I'm sure you're very nice and all that,
但我不需要任何的"智能"东西
but I don't need everything to be smart.
我要去来一杯白痴威士忌
I'm gonna go get a dumb Scotch,
吃点傻子花生 坐在弱智椅子上了
eat some dumb peanuts, sit in a dumb chair.
我以前是很棒的舞者 真的
I was a wonderful dancer, I was,
但可惜这不符合我爹想要给我塑造的个性
but it didn't fit what my dad wanted for me.